spacash.com 2018-10-19

# Privacy Policy - SPAcash

We at Live Interactive Chipre LTD (“SPAcash.io,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) have created this privacy policy (this “Privacy Policy”) because we know that you care about how information you provide to us is used and shared. This Privacy Policy applies to the online information collection and use practices with respect to the publicly-available sections (the “Public Areas”) of the SPAcash.io website (the “Website”). By visiting our Website, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the accompanying Terms of Use.

This Privacy Policy and the accompanying Terms of Use do not apply to your usage of our advetising network (the “Platform”). Use of the Platform, including our collection, use, and disclosure of information entered into the Platform, is governed by our separate Platform terms of service (the “Terms of Service”).

### The Information We Collect

When you use the Public Areas of the Website, you may provide us with personally identifiable information about you and your company, such as your company name, your name, title, e-mail address, postal address, and telephone number (collectively, the “Visitor Information”). We do not collect any Visitor Information from you when you visit the Public Areas of the Website unless you provide us with the Visitor Information voluntarily.

We may automatically collect other types of non-personally identifiable information when you visit the Website such as your network location, the IP address of your computer, and what sections of the Website you visit.

Also, the Website may use “cookie” technology to help us collect other non-personally identifiable information and to enhance your experience using the Website. Cookies are small packets of data that a web site stores on your computer’s hard drive so that your computer will “remember” information about your visit. If you do not want the Website to place a cookie on your hard drive, you may be able to turn that feature off on your computer. Please consult your Internet browser’s documentation for information on how to do this. However, if you decide not to accept cookies from our Website, the Website may not function properly.

### How We Use and Share Visitor Information

If you provide us with Visitor Information through the Public Areas of the Website, we will use such Visitor Information to contact you about the products and/or services about which you have expressed interest. We may also use the Visitor Information to inform you about other products and services that may be available through SPAcash.io. Also, we may share Visitor Information with third parties as described below.

We may from time to time share Visitor Information with other companies who may provide you information about the products and services they offer. However, to the extent required by law, you will be given the opportunity to opt-out of such sharing.

In an ongoing effort to better understand our users, we might aggregate Visitor Information that is provided through the Website. In aggregate form, this Visitor Information does not identify you personally. We may share this aggregate data with our affiliates, agents, and business partners. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

We may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples may include providing marketing assistance and customer service. These other companies will have access to the Visitor Information only as necessary to perform their functions and to the extent permitted by law.

If we or any of our affiliated companies (or all or substantially all of our assets or the assets of any of our affiliated companies) are acquired, we expect that the Visitor Information would be transferred along with the other business assets.

To the extent permitted by law, we may also disclose Visitor Information when required by law, court order, or other government or law enforcement authority or regulatory agency, or whenever we believe that disclosing the Visitor Information is necessary or advisable, for example, to protect the rights, property, or safety of SPAcash.io or others.

### Accessing and Modifying Visitor Information and Communication Preferences

Visitors who have provided personally identifiable information may access, remove, review, and/or make changes to their Visitor Information by e-mailing SPAcash.io at privacy@SPAcash.io. In addition, such Visitors may manage their receipt of marketing and non-transactional communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of any SPAcash.io marketing email. Clients cannot opt out of receiving transactional emails related to their account with SPAcash.io. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to process such requests in a timely manner. You should be aware, however, that it is not always possible to completely remove or modify information in our subscription databases.

### How We Protect Visitor Information

We strive to maintain reasonable physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to secure the Visitor Information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. However, we are unable to guarantee that security measures we take will not be penetrated or compromised or that the Visitor Information will remain secure under all circumstances.

### Children

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 through the Website. If you are under 13, please do not give us any personal information. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children to never provide personal information through the Website without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided personal information to us, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.

### External Web Websites

The Website may contain links to third-party web sites. SPAcash.io has no control over the privacy practices or the content of any of our business partners, advertisers, sponsors, or other web sites to which we provide links from the Website. As such, SPAcash.io is not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of web sites to which our Website may link. You should check the applicable privacy policy of the web site sponsor when visiting any other web sites.

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date stated at the top of this Privacy Policy. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. By accessing this Website after we make any such changes to this Privacy Policy, you are deemed to have accepted such changes. Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis.

### How to Contact Us

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact SPAcash.io via e-mail at info@SPAcash.io.
